{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": " It ________ rain this evening. Why don't you take an umbrella?\n",
            "a": "could be        ",
            "b": "must ",
            "c": "might ",
            "d": "had better",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " ________ you help me with the homework?\n",
            "a": "May ",
            "b": "Shall ",
            "c": "Should        ",
            "d": "Will",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " She hasn't eaten anything since yesterday. She ________ be really hungry.\n",
            "a": "might ",
            "b": "will ",
            "c": "must ",
            "d": "can",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " I put my keys on the table, but now it's gone. Someone ________ have taken it.\n",
            "a": "may ",
            "b": "had to ",
            "c": "should        ",
            "d": "would rather",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Daisy is reading her English test because she has a test tomorrow. She ________ be studying.\n",
            "a": "will ",
            "b": "should        ",
            "c": "must ",
            "d": "can",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " We ________ put the fish in the fridge before it spoils.\n",
            "a": "had to ",
            "b": "may ",
            "c": "can ",
            "d": "had better",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Mr. Brown is very rich. He ________ work hard for a living.\n",
            "a": "mustn't        ",
            "b": "shouldn't     ",
            "c": "can't       ",
            "d": "doesn't have to",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Tom has just got a new job. He ________ be very pleased.\n",
            "a": "might ",
            "b": "must ",
            "c": "should        ",
            "d": "will",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Tom panted his room black. It looks dark and dreary. He ________  have chosen another colour.\n",
            "a": "should ",
            "b": "must ",
            "c": "could ",
            "d": "may",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " ________ you carry this bag for me?\n",
            "a": "May ",
            "b": "Should        ",
            "c": "Will ",
            "d": "Shall",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "28",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}